Register of the Russia Missiia (Greece) Records, 1874-1925
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1874-1924
  - Zionism (Folder 24)
- RUSSIAN CHURCH, 1885-1923
  - Anglican church, Relations with (Box 55., Folder 1)
  - Athens
    - General. Mainly financial records
      - n.d. (Folder 2)
      - 1885-1902 (Folder 3)
      - 1902-1906 (Folder 4)
      - 1912 (Folder 5)
      - 1913 (Folder 6)
      - 1914 (Folder 7)
      - 1914-1915 (Folder 8)
      - 1915 (Folder 9)
      - 1915-1916 (Folder 10)
      - 1916 (Box 56., Folder 1)
      - 1917 (Folder 2-3)
      - 1918 (Folder 4-5)
      - 1919 (Folder 6-9)
    - Antonii, Kievskii. See Platon Khersonskii
    - Iur'ev, Porfirii (Box 57., Folder 1)
    - Leontii, Archimandrite (Folder 2)
    - Platon Khersonskii (Folder 3)
    - Sergii, Archimandrite
      - 1914-1915 (Folder 4)
      - 1916-1919 (Folder 5)
      - 1919 (Folder 6)
      - 1920 (Folder 7)
      - 1923 (Folder 8)
  - Athos, Mount
    - General
      - n.d. (Folder 9)
      - 1898-1911 (Folder 10)
      - 1912 (Folder 11)
      - 1913
        - January (Folder 12)
        - February (Folder 13)
        - March (Folder 14)
        - April (Folder 15)
        - May (Folder 16)
        - June (Folder 17)
        - July (Folder 18)
        - August (Folder 19)
        - September (Folder 20)
        - October (Folder 21)
        - November (Folder 22)
        - December (Folder 23)
      - 1914 (Box 58., Folder 1)
      - 1915
        - Correspondence (Folder 2)
        - Petition (Folder 3)
      - 1916
        - Correspondence (Folder 4)
        - Petition (Folder 5)
      - 1917
        - Clipping (Folder 6)
        - Correspondence
          - General (Folder 7)
          - Secret (Folder 8)
      - 1918
        - Correspondence (Folder 9)
        - Reports
          - General (Folder 10)
          - Grammatopulos (Folder 11)
          - Pavlovskii, Aleksei? (Folder 12)
      - 1919
        - General (Folder 13)
        - Petition (Folder 14)
        - Reports (Folder 15)
      - 1920 (Folder 16)
      - 1921 (Folder 17)
      - 1922 (Folder 18)
    - Balkan Wars, 1912-1913. See also General (Folder 19)
    - Belozerskaia obitel', Ascetic settlement (Folder 20)
    - Constitutions
      - General
        - 1912 (Folder 21)
        - 1913 (Box 59., Folder 1)
        - 1918-1919 (Folder 2)
        - 1919 (Folder 3)
        - 1920 (Folder 4)
      - Drafts by
        - Beliaev (Folder 5)
        - Petriaev, A.M. (Folder 6)
        - Serafimov (Folder 7)
    - Donation of 6 May 1916 to (Folder 8)
    - Evfimii Velikii, Kellion (Folder 9)
    - Food supplies to
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Shipwreck (Folder 11)
    - Georgian kellion (Folder 12)
    - Greek Government compulsory loan, 1922 (Folder 13)
    - Karakal?
      - Monastery (Folder 14)
      - Vozdvizheniia kresta kel'ia (Holy Cross Kellion) (Folder 15)
    - Kokhmanskii, business trip to (Folder 16)
    - Monks
      - Arsenii (Folder 17)
      - Denasii (Folder 18)
      - Georgii (Folder 19)
      - Gerasim (Folder 20)
      - Nifont (Folder 21)
      - Petronii (Folder 22)
      - Serafim (Folder 23)
      - Russian Army, Draft to the. See also Serafim (Folder 24)
    - Novyi Afon (New Athos), Monastery, Georgia -- connections with St. Panteleimon Monastery
      - 1915 (Folder 25)
      - 1921 (Folder 26)
    - Nuzla, Estate. See also Pavlovskii, Aleksei/General/ Reports/ n.d.
      - Russian Consulate General, Thessalonike, Archives of the
        - n.d. (Folder 27)
        - 1891 (Folder 28)
        - 1896 (Folder 29)
        - 1898 (Folder 30)
        - 1900 (Folder 31)
        - 1901 (Folder 32)
        - 1902 (Folder 33)
        - 1903 (Folder 34)
        - 1904 (Folder 35)
        - 1905 (Box 60., Folder 1)
        - 1906 (Folder 2)
        - 1907 (Folder 3)
        - 1908 (Folder 4)
        - 1909 (Folder 5)
        - 1910 (Folder 6)
        - 1911 (Folder 7)
        - 1912 (Folder 8)
        - 1913 (Folder 9)
        - 1919 (Folder 10)
      - Russian Mission, Athens, Archives of the
        - n.d. (Folder 11)
        - 1914 (Folder 12)
        - 1915 (Folder 13)
        - 1916 (Folder 14)
        - 1919 (Folder 15)
        - 1920 (Folder 16)
        - 1921 (Folder 17)
    - Pavlovskii, Aleksei. See also General/ 1918/Reports/ General
      - General
        - Calling cards (Folder 18)
        - Certificate (Folder 19)
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1919 (Folder 20)
          - Incoming
            - n.d. (Folder 21)
            - 1913-1918 (Folder 22)
            - 1919 (Folder 23)
            - 1920 (Folder 24)
            - 1921 (Box 61., Folder 1)
          - Outgoing, 1913-1918 (Folder 2)
        - Diaries (Folder 3)
        - Financial records. See also Correspondence/ General; and Correspondence/Incoming/ 1913-1918 (Folder 4)
        - List of deceased monks. See also Correspondence/General; and Correspon- dence/Incoming/ 1913-1918 (Folder 5)
        - Medical records (Folder 6)
        - Petitions (Folder 7)
        - Printed matter (Folder 8)
        - Reports
          - n.d. (Folder 9)
          - 1917 (Folder 10)
          - 1918 (Folder 11)
          - 1919 (Folder 12)
          - 1920 (Folder 13)
      - Bratstvo russkikh keleinykh obitelei (Russian Kellion Brotherhood) (Folder 14)
      - Commission on Palestine amd Mount Athos. See Paris, Conference of. Commission on Palestine and Mount Athos
      - Constitution of Mount Athos (Folder 15)
      - Iverskii, Monastery (Folder 16)
      - Paris, Conference of. Commission on Palestine and Mount Athos (Folder 17)
      - Property
        - General (Folder 18)
        - Books (Folder 19)
      - Soiuz pomoshchi russkim v Gretsii (Russian Assistance Union in Greece) (Folder 20)
      - "Sviatoimennaia gora afonskaia (Holy Mount Athos)." Typewritten copy of a treatise (Folder 21)
      - Theaters in Athens (Folder 22)
      - Vsemirnyi vestnik ob"iavlenii (World Advertisement Herald) (Folder 23)
    - Prodrom, Romanian skete (Box 62., Folder 1)
    - Religious movement of 1913 (Folder 2)
    - Romanian skete. See Prodrom
    - Serbs in Austria (Folder 3)
    - Sergii, Archimandrite (Folder 4)
    - Taxes. See also Greek Government compulsory loan, 1922 (Folder 5)
    - World War I, 1914-1918
      - British troops. See French and British troops on the peninsula
      - French and British troops on the peninsula (Folder 6)
      - French and Russian troops on the peninsula (Folder 7)
      - Russian troops. See French and Russian troops on the peninsula
  - Catholic Church. See Vysshee russkoe tserkovnoe upravlenie
  - Chapel of a Russian detachment in Makedhonia. See Russian troops in Makedhonia
  - German, Russian monk (Folder 8)
  - Gordeev, Ioann. See German, Russian monk
  - Meletius, Metropolitan of Athens. See USSR/Vysshee upravlenie Rossiiskoi pravoslavnoi tserkvi Sibiri
  - Platon, Archimandrite. See German, Russian monk
  - Russian troops
    - Makedhonia, In (Folder 9)
    - Miraculous assistance to the (Folder 10)
  - USSR. See also Russian troops
    - General (Folder 11)
    - Tikhon, Patriarch. See General
    - Vysshee upravlenie Rossiiskoi pravoslavnoi tserkvi Sibiri (Supreme Administration of Russian Orthodox Church in Siberia), 1919 (Folder 12)
  - Vysshee russkoe tserkovnoe upravlenie zagranitsei (Supreme Administration of Russian Church Abroad) (Folder 13)
  - World War I. See Russian troops
- RUSSIAN CONSULATES IN BALKAN COUNTRIES AND IN TURKEY, 1913-1924
  - General
    - n.d. (Box 63., Folder 1)
    - 1915
      - Greece (Folder 2)
      - Turkey (Folder 3)
    - 1916
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Turkey (Folder 5)
    - 1916-1917 (Folder 6)
    - 1917 (Folder 7-8)
    - 1918 (Folder 9)
    - 1920 (Folder 10)
    - 1921-1922 (Folder 11)
    - 1922 (Folder 12)
  - Bitola (Folder 13)
  - Cephalonia
    - 1916 (Folder 14)
    - 1917 (Folder 15)
    - 1920 (Folder 16)
    - 1921 (Folder 17)
  - Chania
    - n.d. (Folder 18)
    - 1913 (Folder 19)
    - 1916
      - General (Box 64., Folder 1)
      - Personnel (Folder 2)
    - 1917
      - Correspondence (Folder 3)
      - Reports (Folder 4)
    - 1918
      - Correspondence (Folder 5)
      - Report (Folder 6)
    - 1919
      - Correspondence (Folder 7)
      - Report (Folder 8)
    - 1920
      - Correspondence (Folder 9)
      - Financial records (Folder 10)
    - 1921 (Folder 11)
    - 1922 (Folder 12)
    - 1923 (Folder 13)
  - Chios
    - 1916
      - January-July (Box 65., Folder 1)
      - August-November (Folder 2)
    - 1917 (Folder 3)
    - 1918 (Folder 4)
    - 1919 (Folder 5)
    - 1920 (Folder 6)
    - 1921 (Folder 7)
    - 1922 (Folder 8)
    - 1923 (Folder 9)
  - Corfu
    - 1915 (Folder 10)
    - 1916
      - Correspondence (Folder 11)
      - Reports (Folder 12)
    - 1917 (Folder 13)
    - 1918 (Folder 14)
  - Crete. See Chania
  - Dedegach (Folder 15)
  - Ioannina
    - General
      - n.d. (Folder 16)
      - 1915-1916 (Folder 17)
      - 1917. See also 1918
        - General
          - Correspondence (Folder 18)
          - Reports
            - Finance (Folder 19)
            - Politics (Box 66., Folder 1)
        - (Re)opening of the consulate (Folder 2)
      - 1918
        - Correspondence (Folder 3)
        - Financial report (Folder 4)
      - 1919 (Folder 5)
    - Khadzhi-Lazzaro (Folder 6)
  - Izmir
    - 1915 (Folder 7)
    - 1916 (Folder 8)
    - 1919
      - Correspondence (Folder 9)
      - Financial report (Folder 10)
    - 1919-1920 (Folder 11)
    - 1920 (Box 67., Folder 1)
    - 1921 (Folder 2)
    - 1922 (Folder 3)
  - Kalamata
    - 1916 (Folder 4)
    - 1920 (Folder 5)
    - 1921 (Folder 6)
  - Kavalla
    - 1916
      - Budget (Folder 7)
      - Opening of the vice consulate (Folder 8)
    - 1917 (Folder 9)
    - 1919 (Folder 10)
  - Kerkira. See Corfu
  - Mitilini. See also Izmir (Folder 11)
  - Patras
    - 1916
      - Correspondence (Folder 12)
      - Financial records (Folder 13)
    - 1917 (Folder 14)
    - 1918 (Folder 15)
    - 1919 (Folder 16)
    - 1920 (Folder 17)
    - 1920-1921 (Folder 18)
  - Pireus
    - Correspondence
      - 1917 (Folder 19)
      - 1919 (Folder 20)
      - 1920 (Folder 21)
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 22)
      - 1923 (Folder 23)
      - 1923-1924 (Folder 24)
    - Financial records
      - 1920
        - General (Folder 25)
        - Reports (Box 68., Folder 1)
      - 1921
        - January-June (Folder 2)
        - July-December (Folder 3)
      - 1922
        - Appendices (Folder 4)
        - Supporting documents
          - January-June (Folder 5)
          - July-December (Folder 6)
      - 1923 (Folder 7)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 69., Folder 1)
      - 1924 (Folder 2)
    - Journal of cargo ships visiting Pireus port (Folder 3)
    - List of the consulate property transferred to Soviet diplomats (Folder 4)
  - Preveza
    - 1916 (Folder 5)
    - 1917 (Folder 6)
  - Rhodes. See also Izmir
    - 1915-1916 (Folder 7)
    - 1916
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Alad'ev, Solomon (Folder 9)
    - 1917
      - Correspondence (Folder 10)
      - Financial records (Folder 11)
    - 1918 (Folder 12)
    - 1918-1919 (Folder 13)
    - 1919 (Folder 14)
    - 1920 (Folder 15)
    - 1923 (Folder 16)
  - Soviet diplomats in Greece. See Pireus/List of the consulate property transferred to Soviet diplomats
  - Syros
    - 1916 (Box 70., Folder 1)
    - 1917 (Folder 2)
    - 1918 (Folder 3)
    - 1919 (Folder 4)
    - 1920 (Folder 5)
    - 1920-1921 (Folder 6)
  - Thessalonike
    - General
      - Correspondence
        - 1913 (Folder 7)
        - 1916 (Folder 8)
        - 1917 (Folder 9)
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 10)
        - 1918 (Folder 11)
        - 1919 (Folder 12)
        - 1920 (Folder 13)
        - 1921 (Folder 14)
        - 1922 (Folder 15)
        - 1923 (Folder 16)
      - Financial records
        - 1914-1915 (Folder 71., Folder 1)
        - 1916
          - Russian hospital (Folder 2)
          - Russian intelligence service (Folder 3)
        - 1917
          - General (Folder 4)
          - Russian hospital (Folder 5)
        - 1918 (Folder 6)
        - 1919 (Folder 7)
        - 1921
          - General (Folder 8)
          - Receipts (Folder 9)
        - 1922 (Folder 10)
        - 1923 (Folder 11)
    - Grain donated by Nikolai II to the people of Montenegro, Sales of the
      - 1916-1917 (Box 72., Folder 1)
      - 1919-1922 (Folder 2)
    - Kal' (Folder 3)
    - Nikolai II. See Grain donated by Nikolai II to the people of Montenegro
    - Montenegro. See Grain donated by Nikolai II to the people of Montenegro
  - Vlore (Folder 4)
- RUSSIANS IN FOREIGN COUNTRIES, 1915-1925
  - General
    - n.d. (Box 72., Folder 5)
    - 1915-1916 (Folder 6)
    - 1917 (Folder 7)
    - 1918 (Box 73., Folder 1)
    - 1919
      - General
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Folder 8)
        - August (Folder 9)
        - September (Folder 10)
        - October (Folder 11)
        - November (Folder 12)
        - December (Folder 13)
      - Certificates (Folder 14)
      - Reference letters. See Certificates
    - 1920
      - January (Folder 15)
      - February (Folder 16)
      - March (Folder 17)
      - April (Box 74., Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Folder 8)
      - December (Folder 9)
    - 1921
      - General
        - January (Folder 10)
        - February (Folder 11)
        - March (Folder 12)
        - April (Folder 13)
        - May (Folder 14)
        - June (Folder 15)
        - July (Folder 16)
        - August (Folder 17)
        - September (Box 75., Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - Certificates. See Identifications
      - Identifications (Folder 5)
      - Inquiries (Folder 6)
      - Reference letters (Folder 7)
    - 1922 (Folder 8)
    - 1923 (Folder 9)
    - 1924 (Folder 10)
    - 1925 (Folder 11)
  - Addresses (Folder 12)
  - Adler, Anna (Folder 13)
  - Aivaza, Iakov (Folder 14)
  - All-Slav Congress in Belgrad, 1919, Appeal to the (Folder 15)
  - Anti-Bolshevik propaganda. See All-Slav Congress in Belgrad, 1919; League of Nations/ 1921-1922; and Veterans/Cossacks/Krasnov
  - Athens (Folder 16)
  - Baker, Noel. See League of Nations/ 1921-1922
  - Bobrovskii, Petr. See Krym, Solomon
  - Bokhzharov, Andrei (Folder 17)
  - Bolsheviks and Bolshevik sympathizers
    - General
      - n.d. (Folder 18)
      - 1923 (Folder 19)
      - 1924 (Folder 20)
    - Dostavalov (Folder 21)
    - Kogan (Folder 22)
    - Lazarev. See Dostavalov
    - Panchenko, Vasilii (Folder 23)
    - Volianskii, Andrei (Folder 24)
    - Zakhar'in, Ivan (Folder 25)
  - Claims
    - Odintsov, D.A. (Folder 26)
    - Patris, Passenger ship (Box 76., Folder 1)
    - Rogotti, Elise (Folder 2)
    - Sifneo, Vasilii (Folder 3)
    - Sosnovskii (Folder 4)
  - Draft to the Greek military service
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Benlis, Nicolas (Folder 6)
    - Levi, Ruben (Folder 7)
  - Eksportno-importnyi i promyshlennyi bank (Export-Import and Industrial Bank), Odessa (Folder 8)
  - Employment
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Agriculture
      - Thessalonike (Folder 10)
      - Thrace (Folder 11)
    - Boshniak, Leonid (Folder 12)
    - Engineers. See also Railroads/Podderegin, A. (Folder 13)
    - Mines (Folder 14)
    - Railroads
      - General (Folder 15)
      - Podderegin, A. (Folder 16)
    - Real estate (Folder 17)
    - Veterans (Folder 18)
  - Evacuations
    - 1916-1917
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Ismeni, Passenger ship (Folder 20)
    - 1919 (Folder 21)
    - 1920. See also RUSSIANS IN FOREIGN COUNTRIES/Grants and loans/American charitable organizations/American Red Cross (Folder 22)
  - Gil'debrandt (Folder 23)
  - Girs, Mikhail. See League of Nations/ 1921-1922
  - Gorenko, Mariia (Folder 24)
  - Gorlovskii, Anatolii (Folder 25)
  - Grants and loans. See also Employment/Real estate; and Refugee organizations
    - General (Folder 26)
    - American charitable organizations
      - General (Folder 27)
      - American Central Committee for Russian Relief (Folder 28)
      - American Red Cross (Folder 29)
    - Amira, N. (Folder 30)
    - Bul', Konstantin (Folder 31)
    - Greek government
      - 1919 (Folder 32)
      - 1924 (Folder 33)
    - Grekov family (Folder 34)
    - Iankevskii (Box 77., Folder 1)
    - Ianushevich (Folder 2)
    - Kakliugina (Folder 3)
    - Kuskov, Dmitrii (Folder 4)
    - Lyshchinskii (Folder 5)
    - Monastyrskii (Folder 6)
    - Rules and regulations by the Russian Imperial Government (Folder 7)
    - Russian consulates. Financial reports
      - Chania
        - 1916
          - General (Folder 8)
          - Syria, Refugees from (Folder 9)
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 10)
      - Crete. See Chania
      - Pireus
        - 1916 (Folder 11)
        - 1917 (Folder 12)
        - 1919 (Folder 13)
      - Rhodes (Folder 14)
      - Thessalonike (Folder 15)
      - Volos (Folder 16)
    - Sychev, Ivan (Folder 17)
    - Veterans returning to Russia (Folder 18)
  - Greece
    - Compulsory loan
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Greek Ministry of Foreign Affairs (Folder 20)
      - Russian consulates (Folder 21)
    - Legal status, laws etc. in (Folder 22)
  - Greek refugees. See League of Nations/ 1922
  - Greek legion. See Employment/Veterans
  - Greek police (Folder 23)
  - Gregor, Freighter (Box 78., Folder 1)
  - Hoare, Samuel. See League of Nations/ 1921-1922
  - Hospitals. See Refugee Organizations/Rossiiskoe obshchestvo Krasnogo kresta; and Volos and Larisa
  - IAkobson, Miron (Folder 2)
  - Inheritance and succession
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Feodoridi, Georgii (Folder 4)
    - Fulidis, Evstakhii (Folder 5)
    - Golits, Mariia (Folder 6)
    - Kherian, Mateos (Folder 7)
    - Korali (Folder 8)
    - Papazafiropulo, Nikolai (Folder 9)
    - Perdicari, Konstantin (Folder 10)
    - Persiani, Zoia
      - 1919 (Folder 11)
      - 1921 (Folder 12)
    - Russian consulate in Pireus, Files of. See General
    - Shpadier, Marko (Folder 13)
    - Stepanov, Nikolai (Folder 14)
    - Takhmazov, Dionisii. See Tsemin Aleksandr
    - Tsemin, Aleksandr (Folder 15)
  - Isaev, Georgii (Folder 16)
  - Kalachnikov, Ivan (Folder 17)
  - Kamenetskii, N. (Folder 18)
  - Kermidov, Savva (Folder 19)
  - Kharadzhaev, David (Folder 20)
  - Kiril, Grand Duke (Folder 21)
  - Kizil-Adalar (Islands), Turkey (Folder 22)
  - Kokkoli, Vasilissa (Folder 23)
  - Koroleva Ol'ga, Passenger ship (Folder 24)
  - Krym, Liusi. See Krym, Solomon
  - Krym, Solomon (Folder 25)
  - Larisa. See Volos and Larisa
  - Latvia (Folder 26)
  - League of Nations
    - 1921-1922 (Folder 27)
    - 1922 (Folder 28)
  - Leben, Genrikh (Folder 29)
  - Lerkhe, G. (Folder 30)
  - Lodyzhenskii. See League of Nations/ 1921-1922
  - Metaksa, Bazil'
    - 1915 (Folder 31)
    - 1917 (Folder 32)
  - Military cadets. See Passports/Yugoslavia
  - Mud, Ol'ga (Folder 33)
  - Murders
    - Kofman, Tsalik (Folder 34)
    - Sepp, A. (Folder 35)
  - Musin-Pushkin, Aleksei, Count (Folder 36)
  - Nabokov, Sergei. See Krym, Solomon
  - Nabokov, Vladimir. See Krym, Solomon
  - Nansen. See League of Nations/ 1921-1922
  - Naskidov (Folder 37)
  - Neratov. See League of Nations/ 1921-1922
  - Palestine, Pilgrims in (Folder 38)
  - Passports. See also Evacuations; Veterans; and Volos
    - General
      - n.d. (Folder 39)
      - 1913-1916 (Box 79., Folder 1)
      - 1917 (Folder 2)
      - 1918 (Folder 3)
      - 1919 (Folder 4)
      - 1921 (Folder 5)
    - Czechoslovakia (Folder 6)
    - France. See also Italy and France
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Bobovich (Folder 8)
      - Kropotkin, Nikolai, Prince (Folder 9)
      - Nosalevich, Ivan (Folder 10)
      - Tyranov, Ivan (Folder 11)
    - Great Britain (Folder 12)
    - Greece. See also USSR/Ivanova, Mariia
      - General
        - n.d. (Folder 13)
        - 1921 (Folder 14)
      - Litovkin (Folder 15)
    - Italy (Folder 16)
    - Italy and France
      - General (Folder 17)
      - Berezovskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 18)
      - Grigor'ev, Ven'iamin. See Berezovskaia, Ol'ga
      - Nabokov, Vladimir. See General
      - Vishniak, Mark. See General
    - Poland
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Kazarinov, Valerian (Folder 20)
    - Russia. See USSR
    - Serbia. See Yugoslavia
    - Switzerland (Folder 21)
    - Tipolt, Nikolai, Baron. See Switzerland
    - Turkey
      - General (Folder 22)
      - Gul'tiaev, Mikhail (Folder 23)
      - KHokhlov, IA.L. (Folder 24)
      - Pashin, Fedor (Folder 25)
      - Vasil'ev, Ivan (Folder 26)
    - USSR
      - General
        - 1918 (Folder 27)
        - 1919 (Folder 28-29)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 30)
        - 1920
          - General (Folder 31)
          - Veterans (Folder 32)
      - International Red Cross Society (Folder 33)
      - Ivanova, Mariia (Folder 34)
      - Losev, Arsenii (Folder 35)
      - Nabokov, Sergei (Folder 36)
      - Prokoshev, Colonel (Folder 37)
      - Smirnova, Agripina (Folder 38)
      - Zorin, Ivan (Folder 39)
      - Zubenko, Vladimir (Folder 40)
    - USA
      - Kalinin (Folder 41)
      - Khol'mstrem, G.V. (Folder 42)
      - Lozinskii. See Kalinin
      - Sharogradskii, Boris (Folder 43)
    - Yugoslavia
      - n.d. (Folder 44)
      - 1920 (Folder 45)
      - 1921 (Box 80., Folder 1)
  - Pensions
    - 1915 (Folder 2)
    - 1916 (Folder 3)
  - Peterson, Nikolai, Grave of (Folder 4)
  - Petrogradskaia ssudnaia kazna (Petrograd Loan Treasury) (Folder 5)
  - Pireus. See also Athens (Folder 6)
  - Poseidon, Freighter (Folder 7)
  - Property. See also Inheritance and succession; and Requisition by the Greek Government
    - Finland (Folder 8)
    - Girs, A. (Folder 9)
    - Kruglikova, Anastasiia (Folder 10)
    - Osobyi komitet dlia ucheta ubytkov, ponesennykh v sviazi s voinoi russkimi poddannymi vne Rossii (Special Committee for Assessment of War Losses of Russian Subjects outside of Russia) (Folder 11)
    - Poland (Folder 12)
    - Protopopov, S.A. (Folder 13)
    - Sen'ko-Popovskaia (Folder 14)
    - Turkey (Folder 15)
    - World War I, 1914-1918. See Osobyi komitet dlia ucheta ubytkov, ponesennykh v sviazi s voinoi russkimi poddannymi vne Rossii; and Turkey
  - Psaltov, Dimitrii (Folder 16)
  - Refugee organizations
    - General (Folder 17)
    - Biuro trudovoi pomoshchi russkim (Russian Employment Assistance Bureau). See also Komitet trudovoi pomoshchi russkim
      - Athens
        - n.d. (Folder 18)
        - 1921
          - January (Folder 19)
          - February (Folder 20)
          - March (Folder 21)
          - April (Folder 22)
          - May (Folder 23)
          - July (Folder 24)
          - August (Folder 25)
          - September (Folder 26)
          - October (Folder 27)
          - November (Folder 28)
          - December (Folder 29)
        - 1921-1922 (Folder 30)
        - 1922 (Folder 31)
        - 1923 (Folder 32)
      - Thessalonike (Folder 33)
    - Bol'nichnaia kassa russkikh emigrantov v Gretsii (Hospital Insurance of Russian Emigre in Greece) (Folder 34)
    - General Russian Committee for Relief to Russian Refugees, London. See also Glavnyi russkii komitet po delam o bezhentsakh (Box 81., Folder 1)
    - Glavnoe spravochnoe biuro pri Soveshchanii po okazanii pomoshchi russkim bezhentsam (Main Information Bureau of Russian Refugee Relief Committee), Istanbul (Folder 2)
    - Glavnyi russkii komitet po delam o bezhentsakh (General Russian Refugees Committee) (Folder 3)
    - Komitet pomoshchi russkim (Russian Relief Committee), Athens. See also Soiuz pomoshchi russkim v Gretsii (Folder 4)
    - Komitet pomoshchi tuberkuleznym russkim emigrantam (Committee for Assistance to Russian Tubercular Emigrants) (Folder 5)